Emmanuel!
(God with us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Ukeme Essien.
I was trained by
On oil and gas production operations.
Since I completed the training in 2007 December,
I had not had a job for six years.
I have been everywhere, went to so many companies,
did interviews and medical check ups,
but there was always an excuse
why I wasn't given the job.
I came to SCOAN in April this year.
When I came, I got the anointing
water and anointed my self.
That was on Sunday, 7th of April.
I had this oversees connection that refuses to be picking my calls.
Its a recruitment organisation.
Immediately after I anointed myself on that Sunday,
on Monday morning at 7:24 am on the 8th of April,
I received a call from oversees
that they want to see me in the United Arab Emirates
for a face to face interview.
So, they paid my ticket, paid for accommodation in a 5
star hotel in UAE, Abu Dhabi.
Only 35 people were invited for
the interview from all over the world.
Only two people were from Africa from among the 35,
Me and one other man from here in Lagos Nigeria.
When they called me for the interview,
I excused myself to go to the toilet and they approved.
When I got to the toilet, I used the anointing water and....
I sprayed the anointing water all over myself
until I almost emptied the bottle.
I said that, as soon as they see my
face they should see favor,
that I don't want them to ask me
any question I don't know.
And that if there is any question I don't know
if they ask me, they should answer it.
So i got in there, before then, one of the white man that was interviewing
us because I was the list among the 35 - the youngest.
He looked at me, again and again
and I could read his mind.
It was like, "what is this small baby doing here among this adults are gathering?"
So, they called me in; as soon as I opened the door and went in
the white men there started laughing.
Its as If they have known me before.
I was scared; i wondered, could
they be drunk or something?
Any little thing I said, they laugh
and they would be so happy.
They interviewed me for one hour
and for every answer i gave they told me to go deeper and explain more.
After everything, the only question
that they asked me which i did not know.
I spent like 10 seconds trying to
think about it and they answered for me.
So I knew that the anointing water was at work.
They took me for medical check ups
and when i got there, there was an announcement that if
you are more than 45 years old you should come for another check up.
So when I saw the people that were sitting with me stand up,
i joined them to stand up.
So when i got there the American doctor that was doing the check up
said, "Go sit down you are a child, you are a child,
I am talking about adults, you are a child, go sit down."
So everybody started laughing at me
so in the end, they gave me this appointment letter.
Praise the Lord!
I am entitled to a brand new car every two year and
the payment is well over 14 million naira.
That is my payment that is what
they will pay me.
And a very big house going for
4.7 million Naira every year rent.
I decided not to hide such a testimony.
I said I should come and share it for the glory of God.
They made me the field services foreman,
which is the head of all the technicians.
So I thank God.
which I thank God.
The name of the company is
Abu Dhabi company for onshore oil operation.
Its an oil company, this is their clinic where they did my medical check ups.
This is the five star hotel where they lodge me.
{What were you doing before,
from the level you were before to this new level,
tell us?}
Before, I was just moving around teaching in secondary schools.
Yes, and they were paying me 8000 Naira per month.
Teaching part time, in the evening you
will go to school and teach the children.
From morning to evening you will
be moving in the street roaming about.
8000 to millions.}
[Applause]
{This is what I heard from God when
I was given this anointing water.
The transformation will be so great.
Look brother, to go on and on your first salary
you will only take the money you need to for transport and food.
Take it and look round for the less privileged and raise their standard.
[applause]
After that, you can now begin to
remove money that
will not affect you, your living.
Remove it and take it down and continue to take care of the less privileged.
If you do that, in six month you will be transferred
from this place to another place.}
[applause]
Praise the lord!
{Be a good citizen as you are going
please, be a good citizen.
The name of your country, please is very dear.}
Thank you man of God, I am very grateful.
{What is your advice in the whole world
and the people that are still there
where you are coming from.}
Praise God!
First and foremost, I am grateful to the man of God.
I want to advise everyone here that the
Anointing water is one stop shop.
Once you get the anointing water,
whatsoever is the problem is over.
You can Imagine i am the only person
that was selected from Africa.
Just like that, I knew no body there.
But as small as I am, the anointing
water made me great.
I give God all the praise!